[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "brać (też w znaczeniu pić, jeść)",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "tomar",
        "answer1": "tomo",
        "answer2": "tomas",
        "answer3": "toma",
        "answer4": "tomamos",
        "answer5": "tomáis",
        "answer6": "toman",
        "interval": 488,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-10-17",
        "easinessFactor": 2.06,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 6,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "wino",
        "question1": "Nie pijam wina",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "el vino",
        "answer1": "No bebo vino",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-22",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "jeden",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "uno",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-22",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "dwa",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "dos",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-22",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "trzy ",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "tres",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-22",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "cztery",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "cuatro",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-24",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "pięć",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "cinco",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-24",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "sześć",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "seis",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 546,
        "repetitionDate": "2024-11-24",
        "easinessFactor": 2.2,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "siedem",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "siete",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 632,
        "repetitionDate": "2025-03-15",
        "easinessFactor": 2.36,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "isTaught": true,
        "isVerbIrregular": true,
        "question": "osiem",
        "question1": "",
        "question2": "",
        "answer": "ocho",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": "",
        "answer4": "",
        "answer5": "",
        "answer6": "",
        "interval": 653,
        "repetitionDate": "2025-05-16",
        "easinessFactor": 2.26,
        "numberOfCorrectRepetitions": 5,
        "numberOfIncorrectRepetitions": 0
    }
]